heavens-above.com 2018-05-02

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us.

The Heavens-Above and Heavens-Above Pro Android apps operate on the following principles:

  1. We don’t ask for your personal information unless we truly need it.
  2. We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  3. We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Heavens-Above GmbH ("Heavens-Above") operates the website heavens-above.com as well as the Heavens-Above and Heavens-Above Pro Android apps. It is Heavens-Above's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website and applications.

### Website Visitors

Like most website and app operators, Heavens-Above collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Heavens-Above’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Heavens-Above’s visitors and customers use its products. From time to time, Heavens-Above may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by displaying maps showing the distribution of visitors around the world, and daily statistics of web page usage. 

Heavens-Above also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Heavens-Above only discloses IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that the IP address of logged-in users who post comments on the website's online forum are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the forum where the comment was left. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Heavens-Above’s website choose to interact with Heavens-Above in ways that require Heavens-Above to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Heavens-Above gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who want to create a personalized user account to provide a username and email address. In each case, Heavens-Above collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Heavens-Above. Heavens-Above does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Heavens-Above discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Heavens-Above’s behalf or to provide services available at Heavens-Above’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees may be located outside of your home country; by using Heavens-Above’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Heavens-Above will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, as described above, Heavens-Above discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Heavens-Above believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Heavens-Above, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the Heavens-Above website and have supplied your email address, Heavens-Above may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Heavens-Above and our products. We primarily use our website itself to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. Heavens-Above takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Heavens-Above uses cookies to help Heavens-Above identify and track visitors, their usage of Heavens-Above website, and their website access preferences. Heavens-Above visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Heavens-Above’s website, with the drawback that certain features of Heavens-Above’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Heavens-Above, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Heavens-Above goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Heavens-Above may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Heavens-Above and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Heavens-Above may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Heavens-Above’s sole discretion. Heavens-Above encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

This Privacy Policy is based on the one at http://automattic.com/privacy/ – thanks very much to WordPress.com for allowing the world to re-use their content via a Creative Commons Attribution Sharealike license.

  |   | 

Developed and maintained by [Chris Peat](mailto:Chris.Peat@heavens-above.com), Heavens-Above GmbH. Please read the FAQ before sending e-mail. Imprint. 

---|---|---
